A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.20-1.23 (A94-A97) FA471
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A96), 1965-1996; bulk; 1.22; 50.4 Cubic Feet; 42 record cartons. Boxes R2925-R2694.
  - Arts and Humanities (AH)
    - AH 9203 - NATIONAL JAZZ SERVICE ORGANIZATION - EDUCATION AND PUBLIC INFORMATION, 1989-1993 (Box R2955)
    - AH 9025 - NATIONAL HISPANIC MEDIA INSTITUTE - "A BOWL OF BEINGS", 1991-1994 (Box R2955)
    - AH 9208 - PEOPLE'S THEATRE COALITION - FREE IDEA ZONE, 1991-1994 (Box R2955)
    - AH 9209 - PAN AFRICAN ORCHESTRA - 1992 AFRICAN CONCERT SERIES, 1991-1993 (Box R2955)
    - AH 9211 - GUADALUPE CULTURAL ARTS CENTER - MASTER ARTISTS RESIDENCIES, 1988-1995 (Box R2955)
    - AH 9214 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON CULTURE AND DEVELOPMENT, 1992-1994 (Box R2955)
    - AH 9215 - CHARTER SEVENTY-SEVEN FOUNDATION, INC. - LATIN AMERICAN PARTICIPATION IN CONFERENCE "JUSTICE IN TIMES OF TRANSITION", 1991-1994 (Box R2955)
    - AH 9216 - HONOLULU SYMPHONY SOCIETY - 1992-1993 COMPOSER-IN-RESIDENCE PROGRAM, 1991-1994 (Box R2955)
    - AH 9218 - UNITED NATIONS - PROMOTING ASIAN PRESS: SEMINAR EXPENSES, 1992-1993 (Box R2955)
    - AH 9219 - CENTER FOR AFRICAN ART - CONFERENCE "AFRICA BY DESIGN", 1992-1995 (Box R2955)
    - AH 9221 - MEET THE COMPOSER, INC.- "AIDS QUILT SONGBOOK 1992" CONCERT, 1992, 1995 (Box R2955)
    - AH 9222 - PERSEVERANCE THEATRE- RESIDENT COMPANY, 1988-1993 (Box R2956)
    - AH 9223 - RELACHE, INC. - PHILADELPHIA LATINO ARTS AND EDUCATION PROJECT, 1991-1993 (Box R2956)
    - AH 9224 - BROOKLYN HISTORICAL SOCIETY - STONEWALL EXHIBITION PROJECT, 1991-1993 (Box R2956)
    - AH 9225 - BAY AREA WOMEN'S PHILHARMONIC - LATIN WOMEN COMPOSERS, 1989-1994 (Box R2956)
    - AH 9226 - INTERNATIONAL ARTS RELATIONS, INC. - AMERICA'S VISUAL ARTS PROJECT, 1992-1993 (Box R2956)
    - AH 9228 - AMERICAN COMPOSERS ORCHESTRA, INC. - MUSIC OF AMERICAS PROGRAM, 1992-1993 (Box R2956)
    - AH 9232 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - DEVELOPMENT HISTORY, 1985-1996 (Box R2956)
    - AH 9232 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - DEVELOPMENT HISTORY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R2956)
    - AH 9233 - NORTH AMERICAN CONGRESS ON LATIN AMERICA, INC. - PUBLISH "REPORT ON THE AMERICAS", 1991-1992 (Box R2956)
    - AH 9234 - UNIVERSITY OF PITTSBURGH - BC CONFERENCE: "STUDY OF AFRICAN MUSIC AND DANCE - PROBLEMS AND PROSPECTS", 1991-1993 (Box R2957)
    - AH 9237 - UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND - CHILE CONFERENCE, 1991-1994 (Box R2957)
    - AH 9240 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - COMMUNITY-BASED ARTS PROJECT SYMPOSIUM, 1992 (Box R2957)
    - AH 9247 - NATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF ARTISTS' ORGANIZATIONS - CONFERENCE AND EXPAND PARTICIPATION, 1991-1993 (Box R2957)
    - AH 9248 - TEXAS A&M UNIVERSITY - BC CONFERENCE - "ETHICS AND AGRICULTURAL DEVELOPMENT IN AFRICA", 1992-1993 (Box R2957)
    - AH 9254 - ASIAN AMERICAN ARTS CENTRE, INC. - EXHIBITION OF ARTISTS WORK 1945-1965, 1990-1995 (Box R2957)
    - AH 9255 - AMERICAN MUSIC THEATRE FESTIVAL, INC. - "FRIDA" NATIONAL TOUR, 1992-1993 (Box R2957)
    - AH 9256 - JAPANESE AMERICAN CULTURAL AND COMMUNITY CENTER - "CELEBRATE CALIFORNIA" PERFORMANCES, 1989-1994 (Box R2957)
    - AH 9257 - RESOLUTION, INC. - "AFRICAN CINEMA WEEK CELEBRATIONS", 1992-1994 (Box R2957)
    - AH 9258 - AMERICAN UNIVERSITY- BC CONFERENCE: CULTURAL AGENCY/CULTURAL AUTHORITY: POLITICS AND POETICS OF INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY IN THE POST-COLONIAL ERA, 1991-1994 (Box R2957)
    - AH 9260 - NON-TRADITIONAL CASTING PROJECT, INC. - ONLINE COMPUTER SYSTEM ARTISTS FILES ONLINE, 1992-1994 (Box R2958)
    - AH 9261 - UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND - WORKSHOP "SOCIOCULTURAL CONDITIONS", 1992-1994 (Box R2958)
    - AH 9262 - AMERICAN CENTER FOR INTERNATIONAL LEADERSHIP - STUDY SOCIO-POLITICAL CLIMATE IN UZBEKISTAN, 1992-1995 (Box R2958)
    - AH 9263 - CULTURAL SURVIVAL INC. - CULTURAL SURVIVAL CENTER, 1990-1995 (Box R2958)
    - AH 9265 - NATIONAL PUBLIC RADIO - "CULTURAL DESK" PROJECT, 1992-1994 (Box R2958)
    - AH 9266 - AMERICAN SYMPHONY ORCHESTRA LEAGUE - NATIONAL TASK FORCE COMPONENT OF THE AMERICAN ORCHESTRA: AN INITIATIVE FOR CHANGE, 1991-1993 (Box R2958)
    - AH 9268 - ALTERNATE ROOTS, INC. - COMMUNITY/ARTISTS PARTNERSHIP PROJECT, 1991-1994 (Box R2958)
    - AH 9275 - TELEVISION TRUST FOR THE ENVIRONMENT INTERNATIONAL - DATABASE OF ENVIRONMENTAL VIDEOS AND FILMS, 1992-1995 (Box R2958)
    - AH 9277 - SMITH COLLEGE - AFRO-COLOMBIAN RESPONSE TO MODERNIZATION, 1992-1995 (Box R2958)
  - Equal Opportunity (EO)
    - EO 8635 - URBAN UNDERCLASS - EMPLOYMENT OPPORTUNITIES IN WASHINGTON, D.C., 1986-1988 (Box R2959)
    - EO 9108 - NAACP - SPECIAL CONTRIBUTION FUND - STRUCTURAL REORGANIZATION, 1990-1995 (Box R2959)
    - EO 9119 - FUTURE OF WORK TASK FORCE, 1991-1994 (Box R2959)
    - EO 9122 - AMERICAN ENTERPRISE INSTITUTE FOR PUBLIC POLICY RESEARCH - INTEGRATED SERVICES, 1991-1993 (Box R2959)
    - EO 9124 - NCI RESEARCH - EMPLOYMENT STUDY, 1991-1993 (Box R2959)
    - EO 9132 - UNIVERSITY OF MASSACHUSETTS - FAMILY HOMELESSNESS MONOGRAPH, 1991-1993, 1996 (Box R2959)
    - EO 9045 - HUNTER COLLEGE - PUERTO RICAN MIGRATION STUDY, 1990-1994 (Box R2960)
    - EO 9140 - JOINT CENTER FOR POLITICAL AND ECONOMIC STUDIES - DISSEMINATION OF POVERTY STUDY, 1990-1994 (Box R2960)
    - EO 9201 - TEXAS INTERFAITH EDUCATION FUND - JOB TRAINING PILOT PROJECTS, 1991-1996 (Box R2960)
    - EO 9203 - MANPOWER DEMONSTRATION RESEARCH CORP. - JOBSTART FOLLOW UP, 1989-1993 (Box R2960)
    - EO 9203 - MANPOWER DEMONSTRATION RESEARCH CORP. - JOBSTART FOLLOW UP - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R2960)
    - EO 9205 - NATIONAL HOUSING AND COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT LAW PROJECT - CONFERENCE ON PUBLIC HOUSING, 1990-1993 (Box R2961)
    - EO 9206 - JOINT CENTER FOR POLITICAL AND ECONOMIC STUDIES - SIXTH NATIONAL POLICY INSTITUTE CONFERENCE, 1991-1994 (Box R2961)
    - EO 9207 - FAIR EMPLOYMENT COUNCIL OF GREATER WASHINGTON - TESTING FOR EMPLOYMENT DISCRIMINATION CENTRAL CLEARINGHOUSE, 1991-1996 (Box R2961)
    - EO 9208 - ROCKY MOUNTAIN WOMEN'S INSTITUTE- "WOMEN ON TRIAL", 1991-1992, 1996 (Box R2961)
    - EO 9209 - NATIONAL PUERTO RICAN COALITION - RESEARCH ADVOCACY AND POLICY ANALYSIS OFFICE, 1991-1994 (Box R2961)
    - EO 9210 - CITIZENS COMMISSION ON CIVIL RIGHTS - BUSH ADMINISTRATION ENFORCEMENT, 1989-1996 (Box R2961)
    - EO 9212 - NAACP - LEGAL DEFENSE AND EDUCATIONAL FUND - CAPITAL PUNISHMENT PROGRAM, 1991-1992 (Box R2961)
    - EO 9213 - URBAN STRATEGIES COUNCIL - NATIONAL NETWORK ACTIVITIES AND COMMUNICATIONS, 1992-1993 (Box R2961)
    - EO 9215 - LABOR MARKET OUTLOOK - ROUNDTABLES ON LABOR MARKET POLICIES, 1991-1993 (Box R2962)
    - EO 9215 - LABOR MARKET OUTLOOK - ROUNDTABLES ON LABOR MARKET POLICIES - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R2962)
    - EO 9216 - COMMUNITY PARTNERSHIP FOR THE PREVENTION OF HOMELESSNESS - NEIGHBORHOOD-BASED PARTNERSHIPS IN WASHINGTON, D.C., 1991-1992, 1996 (Box R2962)
    - EO 9218 - EQUAL OPPORTUNITY - COMMUNICATIONS PLAN, 1990-1993, 1996; 4 folders. (Box R2962)
    - EO 9218 - EQUAL OPPORTUNITY - COMMUNICATIONS PLAN - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 3 folders. (Box R2963)
    - EO 9219 - GEORGETOWN UNIVERSITY LAW CENTER - CHILD POVERTY IN FAMILY HOMELESSNESS PREVENTION CLINIC, 1992-1994 (Box R2963)
    - EO 9220 - BASIC RIGHTS REVIEW, 1991-1992, 1996 (Box R2963)
    - EO 9221 - NATIONAL ACADEMY OF PUBLIC ADMINISTRATION - CONFERENCE ON REINVENTING GOVERNMENT, 1992-1993 (Box R2963)
    - EO 9226 - AMERICAN JEWISH COMMITTEE - CONFERENCE ON FIGHTING POVERTY, 1992, 1994 (Box R2963)
    - EO 9231 - DEVELOPMENT TRAINING INSTITUTE - HUMAN RESOURCE CRISIS, 1988-1996; 2 folders. (Box R2964)
    - EO 9233 - GREATER WASHINGTON RESEARCH CENTER - "EVALUATION OF PROSPECTS FOR COMMUNITY-BASED ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT", 1992-1994 (Box R2964)
    - EO 9234 - NATIONAL HISPANIC LEADERSHIP AGENDA - HISPANIC ISSUES AWARENESS, 1991-1994 (Box R2964)
    - EO 9236 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY- AFRICAN AMERICAN COMMUNITY STUDY, 1989-1994 (Box R2964)
    - EO 9237 - ASSOCIATION OF BLACK FOUNDATION EXECUTIVES - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1990-1993 (Box R2964)
    - EO 9238 - COMMUNITY PLANNING AND ACTION RETREAT - CONFERENCE OF THE CPAP PROJECTS, 1992-1993 (Box R2964)
    - EO 9239 - NAACP - SPECIAL CONTRIBUTIONS FUND - EXECUTIVE SEARCH COMMITTEE, 1992-1993 (Box R2964)
    - EO 9240 - POVERTY AND RACE RESEARCH ACTION COUNCIL - EVALUATION OF PRRAC ADMINISTRATIVE AND MANAGEMENT OPERATIONS, 1992-1996 (Box R2964)
    - EO 9241 - MANPOWER DEMONSTRATION RESEARCH CORP. - STUDY THE BEHAVIOR OF ETHNIC GROUPS IN WELFARE EMPLOYMENT PROGRAMS, 1992-1996 (Box R2964)
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A97), 1966, 1969-1997, 2004; bulk; 1.23; 129.6 Cubic Feet; 108 record cartons. Boxes R2965-R3072.
  - United States, 200
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 200D
      - WINROCK INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE FOR AGRICULTURAL DEVELOPMENT- RECORDS MANAGEMENT, 1985-1986 (Box R2965)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, 200E
      - SHERWOOD, STEVEN W., 1983-1986 (Box R2965)
    - United States - Population Studies, 200P
      - POPULATION COUNCIL - NORPLANT USE IN CHINA, 1983-1989; 2 folders. (Box R2965)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 200R
      - ASIA SOCIETY - ASIA TOWARD YEAR 2000 CONFERENCE, 1981-1984 (Box R2976)
      - ASIA SOCIETY - ASIA TOWARD YEAR 2000 CONFERENCE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R2976)
      - ATLANTIC CENTER FOR THE ARTS, 1981-1986 (Box R2976)
      - ATLANTIC CENTER FOR THE ARTS, 1980 (Box R2977)
      - ATLANTIC CENTER FOR THE ARTS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R2977)
      - BROWN UNIVERSITY - GENDER RESEARCH IN THIRD WORLD COUNTRIES, 1983-1987 (Box R2977)
      - FLORIDA - CULTURAL AFFAIRS - CONFERENCE, 1983-1986 (Box R2977)
      - STANFORD UNIVERSITY - BAGEP, 1983-1989 (Box R2977)
      - STANFORD UNIVERSITY - BAGEP - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R2977)
      - UNIVERSITY OF DELAWARE - ETHICAL ISSUES, 1979-1986 (Box R2977)
      - UNIVERSITY OF DELAWARE - ETHICAL ISSUES - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R2977)
    - EMPLOYMENT PROGRAM FOR MINORITY-GROUP - FEMALE SINGLE PARENTS, 1981-1994; Complete file includes 9 folders, and 7 supplementary material folders across R3062-R3065. (Box R3062)
    - EMPLOYMENT PROGRAM FOR MINORITY-GROUP - FEMALE SINGLE PARENTS, 1981-1994; Complete file includes 9 folders, and 7 supplementary material folders across R3062-R3065. (Box R3063)
    - EMPLOYMENT PROGRAM FOR MINORITY-GROUP - FEMALE SINGLE PARENTS, 1981-1994; Complete file includes 9 folders, and 7 supplementary material folders across R3062-R3065. (Box R3064)
    - EMPLOYMENT PROGRAM FOR MINORITY-GROUP - FEMALE SINGLE PARENTS, 1981-1994; Complete file includes 3 folders, and 2 supplementary material folders across R3066-R3067. (Box R3065)
    - EMPLOYMENT PROGRAM FOR MINORITY-GROUP - FEMALE SINGLE PARENTS - EVALUATION, 1982, 1986-1987; Complete file includes 3 folders, and 2 supplementary material folders across R3066-R3067. (Box R3066)
    - EMPLOYMENT PROGRAM FOR MINORITY-GROUP - FEMALE SINGLE PARENTS - EVALUATION, 1982, 1986-1987; 2 folders. (Box R3067)
    - EMPLOYMENT PROGRAM FOR MINORITY-GROUP - FEMALE SINGLE PARENTS - EVALUATION (ABT ASSOCIATES) - AGREEMENTS, 1982-1987 (Box R3068)
    - EMPLOYMENT PROGRAM FOR MINORITY-GROUP - FEMALE SINGLE PARENTS - CHILD CARE POLICY, 1988-1989, 1992; Complete file includes: 7 folders and 8 supplementary material folders across R3069-R3071. (Box R3069)
    - EMPLOYMENT PROGRAM FOR MINORITY-GROUP - FEMALE SINGLE PARENTS - EVALUATION (MATHEMATICA POICY RESEARCH), 1985-1994; Complete file includes: 7 folders and 8 supplementary material folders across R3069-R3071. (Box R3069)
    - EMPLOYMENT PROGRAM FOR MINORITY-GROUP - FEMALE SINGLE PARENTS - EVALUATION (MATHEMATICA POICY RESEARCH), 1985-1994; Complete file includes: 7 folders and 8 supplementary material folders across R3069-R3071. (Box R3070)
    - EMPLOYMENT PROGRAM FOR MINORITY-GROUP - FEMALE SINGLE PARENTS - EVALUATION (MATHEMATICA POICY RESEARCH), 1985-1994 (Box R3071)
    - EMPLOYMENT PROGRAM FOR MINORITY-GROUP - FEMALE SINGLE PARENTS - EVALUATION (MATHEMATICA POICY RESEARCH) - AGREEMENTS, 1986-1988 (Box R3072)
    - EMPLOYMENT PROGRAM FOR MINORITY-GROUP - FEMALE SINGLE PARENTS - ROUSE, 1986 (Box R3072)
  - Puerto Rico, 243
    - PUERTO RICO COMMUNITY FOUNDATION, 1983-1989 (Box R2965)
  - Brazil, 305
    - UNIVERSITY OF CAMPINAS - TELLES, 1987-1991 (Box R2966)
    - UNIVERSITY OF MINAS GERAIS - GOZA, 1985-1990 (Box R2966)
    - UNIVERSITY OF MINAS GERAIS - LOVELL, 1988-1991 (Box R2966)
    - UNIVERSITY OF MINAS GERAIS - SCHMERTMANN, 1987-1990 (Box R2966)
  - England, 401
    - ANTI-SLAVERY SOCIETY - CHILD LABOR, 1981-1985, 1991 (Box R2966)
    - ANTI-SLAVERY SOCIETY - CHILD LABOR - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R2966)
  - India, 464
    - ADMINISTRATION, 1975 (Box R2966)
  - China, 601
    - STATE FAMILY PLANNING COMMISSION - HEREWARD, 1990-1994; 2 folders. (Box R2967)
    - China - Natural Sciences, 601D
      - CHINESE ACADEMY OF AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES - GERMPLASM - AGREEMENTS, 1981-1987; 2 folders. (Box R2967)
      - CHINESE ACADEMY OF AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES - GERMPLASM, 1985-1990; 7 folders. (Box R2967)
      - CHINESE ACADEMY OF AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES - GERMPLASM, 1979-1984 (Box R2968)
      - CHINESE ACADEMY OF AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES - GERMPLASM - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R2969)
    - China - Population Studies, 601P
      - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - BIOLOGICAL INSTITUTE, 1978-1991 (Box R2969)
      - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - BIOLOGICAL INSTITUTE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R2969)
      - Chinese Academy of Medical Sciences - Contraceptive development, 1979-1990, 1996 (Box R2970)
  - Korea, 613
    - Korea - Population Studies, 613P
      - Yonsei University - Norplant evaluation, 1983-1992 (Box R2970)
  - Thailand, 617
    - Mahidol University - Richter, 1987-1990, 1993 (Box R2970)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, 617E
      - Julapa Rungkasiri, 1980-1990 (Box R2970)
  - Indonesia, 652
    - Indonesia - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, 652E
      - Koswara, Eddy, 1983-1991 (Box R2970)
      - Nasrullah, Trisnowati, 1980-1985 (Box R2970)
      - Sugiono, Mr. Harnik, 1982-1991 (Box R2970)
  - Egypt, 812
    - Cairo Demographic Centre - Guhl, 1987-1988 (Box R2971)
  - 860
    - Adeyemo, Oyewole, 1984-1989 (Box R2971)
    - Cheah, Kathyrn S.E., 1984-1990 (Box R2971)
    - Chen Wei-Feng, 1984-1989 (Box R2971)
    - Ma Jian-Chuan, 1984-1990 (Box R2971)
    - Pental, Deepak, 1984-1992 (Box R2971)
    - Shi Pu-Tao, 1984-1990 (Box R2971)
    - Stoll, Guillermo M., 1984-1991 (Box R2971)
    - Turrens, Julio F., 1984-1987 (Box R2971)
    - Zhu Jia-Bi, 1984-1990 (Box R2971)
  - Program and Policy - Humanities, 911
    - Program and Policy - Humanities - Fellowships, 911E
      - Chambers, John Whiteclay II, 1980-1986 (Box R2971)
      - Frank, Joseph N., 1982-1985 (Box R2971)
      - Gilbert, Sandra, 1981-1983, 1987-1988 (Box R2971)
      - Johns Hopkins University - Resident fellows, 1982-1993 (Box R2971)
      - RICKFORD, JOHN R., 1983-1986; 2 folders. (Box R2974)
      - SMITHSONIAN INSTITUTION - RESIDENT FELLOWS, 1983-1991 (Box R2974)
      - UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND - RESIDENT FELLOWS, 1983-1988 (Box R2974)
      - WALKER ART CENTER - RESIDENT FELLOWS, 1983-1988 (Box R2974)
      - WILSON INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR SCHOLARS - RESIDENT FELLOWS, 1983-1990 (Box R2976)
      - WILSON INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR SCHOLARS - RESIDENT FELLOWS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R2976)
      - YOUNG MEN'S & YOUNG WOMEN'S HEBREW ASSOCIATION (NYC) - RESIDENT FELLOWS, 1983-1988, 1991 (Box R2976)
  - Agricultural Sciences (AS)
    - AS 8845 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE- MAIZE PATHOLOGY PROJECT, 1982-1992, 1996 (Box R2972)
    - AS 8937 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - DRAUGHT ANIMAL POWER, 1989-1995 (Box R2972)
    - AS 8960 - UNIVERSITY OF MINNESOTA - RFLP MAPPING IN VIGNA, 1989-1993, 1996 (Box R2972)
    - AS 9001 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - PLANT AND ANIMAL BIOTECHNOLOGY CONFERENCE, 1989-1992 (Box R2972)
    - AS 9003 - INDIAN SOCIETY OF SEED TECHNOLOGY - SEED SCIENCE CONFERENCE, 1989-1992 (Box R2972)
    - AS 9005 - NATIONAL MUSEUMS OF KENYA - WILDLIFE RESEARCH CONFERENCE, 1989-1992 (Box R2972)
    - AS 9012 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - MAIZE STALK BORERS, 1989-1990, 1996 (Box R2972)
    - AS 9018 - OVERSEAS DEVELOPMENT COUNCIL - RURAL DEVELOPMENT IN THE THIRD WORLD, 1989-1994 (Box R2972)
    - AS 9027 - ASIAN INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY - FARMING SYSTEMS SYMPOSIUM, 1989-1993 (Box R2972)
    - AS 9028 - MICHIGAN STATE UNIVERSITY - FARMING SYSTEMS RESEARCH SYMPOSIUM, 1990-1991 (Box R2972)
    - AS 9032 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - RURAL FOOD SECURITY, 1987-1992 (Box R2972)
    - AS 9036 - UNITED NATIONS - FOOD AND AGRICULTURE ORGANIZATION TREATY MEETING, 1990-1991, 1994-1995 (Box R2973)
    - AS 9038 - EDUARDO MONDLANE UNIVERSITY - AGRICULTURE AND FOREST STUDIES, 1989-1990, 1994 (Box R2973)
    - AS 9040 - WINROCK INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE FOR AGRICULTURAL DEVELOPMENT - ANIMAL AGRICULTURE IN AFRICA, 1990-1994 (Box R2973)
    - AS 9041 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER - CEREAL GRAIN POLICY ANALYSIS IN AFRICA, 1990-1994 (Box R2973)
    - AS 9106 - KANGETHE, LOUIS, 1990-1991, 1996 (Box R2973)
    - AS 9110 - INDIAN SOCIETY OF GENETICS AND PLANT BREEDING - CONFERENCE, 1990-1993 (Box R2973)
    - AS 9112 - WORLD ASSOCIATION OF SOIL AND WATER CONSERVATION - CONFERENCE, 1990-1993 (Box R2973)
    - AS 9114 - RESOURCES DEVELOPMENT FOUNDATION - STEERING COMMITTEE MEETING, 1990-1991 (Box R2973)
    - AS 9115 - ASSOCIATION FOR THE TAXONOMIC STUDY OF THE FLORA OF TROPICAL AFRICA - 13th CONGRESS, 1990-1994 (Box R2973)
    - AS 9117 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - FACULTY OF AGRICULTURE LIBRARY, 1991-1992, 1996 (Box R2973)
    - AS 9118 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF CONTROL - BANANA PEST MANAGEMENT IN UGANDA, 1991-1994 (Box R2973)
    - AS 9119 - DIOUF, JACQUES, 1990-1994 (Box R2973)
    - AS 9124 - SEMOKA, JOHNSON MASHAMBA R., 1991-1993 (Box R2973)
    - AS 9125 - THAILAND DEVELOPMENT RESEARCH INSTITUTE FOUNDATION - AGRICHEMICAL USE IMPACT, 1991-1994 (Box R2973)
    - AS 9126 - EDUARDO MONDLANE UNIVERSITY - STRENGTHENING TRAINING CAPACITY, 1990-1993, 1996 (Box R2973)
    - AS 9129 - MUFANDAEDZA, ONEAS TICHAFA, 1988-1992 (Box R2975)
    - AS 9133 - STANFORD UNIVERSITY - RICE PRODUCTIVITY STUDY, 1991-1993 (Box R2975)
    - AS 9137 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (NIGERIA) - SYMPOSIUM PARTICIPATION OF COSCA, 1991-1993 (Box R2975)
    - AS 9138 - GOLDSMITH, PAUL, 1991-1994 (Box R2975)
    - AS 9140 - SERVICIOS PARA EL DESARROLLO SOCIAL, A.C. - SUSTAINABLE AGRICULTURAL MANAGEMENT IN COSTA RICA, 1991-1992 (Box R2975)
    - AS 9141 - INCREASING KNOWLEDGE FOR THE MANAGEMENT OF NATURAL RESOURES, 1990-1993 (Box R2975)
    - AS 9144 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE- PUBLICATION OF THE CONGRESS PROCEEDINGS, 1991-1994 (Box R2975)
    - AS 9146 - UNIVERSITY OF GEORGIA - METHANE FLUX FROM RICE ECOSYSTEMS ASSESSMENT, 1991-1993 (Box R2975)
    - AS 9148 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (BERKELEY) - LARGER GRAIN BORDER, 1990-1994 (Box R2975)
    - AS 9152 - SADCC REGIONAL GENE BANK FOR PLAN GENETIC RESOURCES - FIRST TRAINING WORKSHOP IN PLANT GENETIC RESOURCES, 1991-1993 (Box R2975)
    - AS 9203 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE OF INSECT PHYSIOLOGY AND ECOLOGY (ICIPE) - "FRIENDS OF ICIPE", 1991-1993, 1996 (Box R2975)
    - AS 9208 - INTERNATIONAL RURAL SOCIOLOGY ASSOCIATION - EIGHTH WORLD CONGRESS AFRICAN PARTICIPATION, 1991-1993 (Box R2975)
    - AS 9209 - YOUTH FOR ACTION - WORKSHOP ON MANAGEMENT OF NATURAL RESOURCES, 1991-1993 (Box R2975)
    - AS 9210 - GESTION DE ECOSISTEMAS ASOCIACION CIVIL - TROPICAL ECOLOGY ADVISORY GROUP, 1991-1993 (Box R2975)
    - AS 9216 - CONSORCIO LATINO AMERICANO SOBRE AGROECOLOGIA Y DESARROLLO (CLADES) - GRADUATE COURSE ON AGROECOLOGY AND SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT, 1992-1993 (Box R2975)
    - AS 9217 - OREGON STATE UNIVERSITY- NATURAL RESOURCES CURRICULUM DEVELOPMENT FOR CHIANG MAIUNIVERSITY, 1992-1996 (Box R2975)
    - AS 9218 - UNIVERSITY OF MINNESOTA - SUSTAINABLE AGRICULTURAL DEVELOPMENT INTO THE 21ST CENTURY PUBLICATIONS, 1988-1994 (Box R2978)
    - AS 9220 - DUANG PRATEEP FOUNDATION - YOUNG WOMEN'S DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM, 1992-1993 (Box R2978)
    - AS 9221 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI - WORSHOP ON STRATEGIC PLANNING FOR AGRICULTURE, 1992-1994 (Box R2978)
    - AS 9223 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - CONFERENCE ON SMALLHOLDER MICRO-IRRIGATION SCHEMES IN ZIMBABWE, 1992-1994 (Box R2978)
    - AS 9224 - AFRICAN METEOROLOGICAL SOCIETY - FIRST INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE, "RECENT CLIMATE ANOMALIES & PREDICTION IN AFRICA", 1992-1995 (Box R2978)
    - AS 9226 - WORLD ASSOCIATION OF SOIL AND WATER CONSERVATION- PROJECT IN AFRICA DEALING WITH ORGANIC MATTER MANAGEMENT RESEARCH & INFO. NEEDS, 1992-1994 (Box R2978)
    - AS 9227 - MALAWI - AGRICULTURE (MINISTRY OF) - PLANT PROTECTION SERVICES WORKSHOP, 1991-1993, 1996 (Box R2978)
    - AS 9228 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - FOR THE PUBLICATION OF THE PROCEEDINGS OF THE SYMPOSIUM, "THE APPLICATION OF GIS IN KENYA", 1992-1994 (Box R2978)
    - AS 9230 - INTERNATIONAL SERVICE FOR NATIONAL AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH (ISNAR) - TOWARD COST OF TRAINING WORKSHOP ON RESEARCH MGT. SKILLS FOR NEW RESEARCH DIRECTORS, 1992-1993 (Box R2978)
    - AS 9231 - INTERNATIONAL COUNCIL FOR RESEARCH IN AGROFORESTRY (ICRAF) - TOWARDS THE COSTS OF ITS 1992 AGROFORESTRY RESEARCH DEVELOPMENT COURSE, 1992-1993, 1996 (Box R2978)
    - AS 9232 - AGRICULTURAL MEDIA SEMINAR, 1989-1996 (Box R2978)
    - AS 9233 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - INTERNATIONAL WORKSHOP ON SLASH/MULCH SYSTEMS, 1992-1994 (Box R2978)
    - AS 9234 - RUTGERS UNIVERSITY - WORKSHOP: CONTROL OF PATHOGENS IN FOOD CROPS, RICE AND CASSAVA, 1991-1993 (Box R2978)
    - AS 9235 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR RESEARCH IN AGROFORESTRY - AGROFORESTRY SYSTEMS IN RWANDA AND BURUNDI, 1992, 1996 (Box R2978)
    - AS 9237 - NATIONAL RESOURCES INSTITUTE - COSTS OF DEVELOPING COUNTRY PARTICIPANTS AT HARARE WORKSHOP, 1991-1995 (Box R2978)
    - AS 9238 - COLEGIO DE POSTGRADUADOS - PUBLISHING RESULTS OF SYMPOSIUM: AGROECOLOGY AND EDUCATION, 1992-1994 (Box R2978)
    - AS 9241 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (IITA) (NIGERIA) - DYNAMICS OF FARMERS RESOURCE MANAGEMENT, FOREST ZONE CAMEROON, 1992-1994 (Box R2978)
    - AS 9243 - INCREASING KNOWLEDGE FOR THE MANAGEMENT OF NATURAL RESOURCES - SUSTAINABLE AGRICULTURE, 1991-1996 (Box R2979)
    - AS 9244 - WORLD RESOURCES INSTITUTE - COMMITTEE ON AGRICULTURAL SUSTAINABILITY, 1991-1994 (Box R2979)
    - AS 9245 - WORLD BANK- 1993 CGIAR MIDTERM MEETING, 1991-1994 (Box R2979)
    - AS 9248 - KASETSART UNIVERSITY - TWO PARTICIPANTS FROM INDIA TO ATTEND CERTIFICATE COURSE IN COMMUNITY FORESTRY, 1992-1993 (Box R2979)
  - Global Environment (GE)
    - GE 9203 - INFORM, INC. - SOURCE REDUCTION WORKSHOP, 1990-1991, 1996 (Box R2979)
    - GE 9204 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF RURAL RECONSTRUCTION - INTERNATIONAL COURSE ON BIOGAS TECHNOLOGIES FOR SMALL FARMS, 1991-1993 (Box R2979)
    - GE 9207 - NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF BIODIVERSITY - BIODIVERSITY PROSPECTING PROJECT (COSTA RICA), 1991-1994 (Box R2979)
    - GE 9209 - REED, THOMAS B. - ADVISE THE CHINESE GOVERNMENT ON GASIFICATION TECHNOLOGY, 1992 (Box R2979)
    - GE 9210 - INTERACTION: AMERICAN COUNCIL FOR VOLUNTARY INTERNATIONAL ACTION, INC. - LATIN AMERICAN PARTICIPATION IN 1992 FORUM (Box R2979)
    - GE 9211 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDAION - BC CONFERENCE: "ECOTOURISM", 1992-1996 (Box R2979)
    - GE 9214 - APPROPRIATE TECHNOLOGY INTERNATIONAL (ATI) - PROJECT IN INDIA ON GREENHOUSE GAS REDUCTION, 1992-1994 (Box R2979)
    - GE 9215 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION INC/GEF CONFERENCE, 1992-1993, 1996 (Box R2979)
    - GE 9220 - INTERNATIONAL OCEAN INSTITUTE - CONFERENCE ON INTERNATIONAL OCEAN MANAGEMENT & OTHER RESOURCES, 1992-1993 (Box R2979)
    - GE 9223 - CONSULTATIVE GROUP ON BIOLOGICAL DIVERSITY (CGBD) - PROGRAM ACTIVITIES, 1988-1995 (Box R2979)